[
{
  "id": 0,
  "question": "What is required for a model to be declared a Warlord?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "Model must be a character",
    "Model must be an infantry model",
    "Model must be at least 2 inches tall"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 0
},
{
  "id": 1,
  "question": "When does a defending unit fire Overwatch?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "After a Charge movement is completed",
    "When a Charge is declared",
    "After the charge attack completes"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 1
},
{
  "id": 2,
  "question": "What is the maximum distance in which a charge can be declared?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "Within 18 inches",
    "Within 12 inches",
    "Within the unit's max charge distance"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 1
},
{
  "id": 3,
  "question": "What is the Warp Charge value of Smite?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "5",
    "5 + 1 for each previous instance of Smite cast during the current phase",
    "5 + 1 for each previous instance of Smite cast during the game"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 1
}
,
{
  "id": 4,
  "question": "In order to benifit from the character targeting rule, how many wounds can a model have?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "At least 5",
    "Less than 8",
    "Less than 10"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 2
},
{
  "id": 5,
  "question": "One turn one, where can a model deploy from reserves?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "Anywhere at least 9 inches from an enemy model",
    "Anywhere at least 9 inches from an enemy model or the enemy deployment zone",
    "Only within the player's own deployment zone"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 2
},
{
  "id": 6,
  "question": "What factions do not need an HQ model in their vanguard detachment?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "Legion of the Damned, Sisters of Battle, Imperial Assasins",
    "Sisters of Battle, Imperial Assasins, Inquistion",
    "Legion of the Damned, Custodes, Imperial Assasins"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 0
},
{
  "id": 7,
  "question": "How many Command Points does a commander get for fielding a battlion detachment?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "6",
    "3",
    "5"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 2
}
,
{
  "id": 8,
  "question": "How many Command Points does a commander get for fielding a brigade detachment?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "6",
    "9",
    "12"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 2
},
{
  "id": 9,
  "question": "How many Command Points does a commander get for fielding a supreme command detachment?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "0",
    "1",
    "2"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 1
},
{
  "id": 10,
  "question": "How often can the Tide of Traitors Strategem be used?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "Once per Phase",
    "Once per Turn",
    "Once per Game"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 2
},
{
  "id": 11,
  "question": "In Organzied play, how many copies of a datasheet can be present in a 2000 point list?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "2 times",
    "3 times",
    "4 times"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 1
},
{
  "id": 12,
  "question": "In Organzied play, how many copies of a datasheet can be present in a 1000 point list?",
  "type": "MultipleChoice",
  "answers": [
    "2 times",
    "3 times",
    "4 times"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": 0
}



]